[{"success": true, "timeout": false, "failed_images": [], "failed_audio": [], "failed_video": [], "trial_type": "preload", "trial_index": 0, "time_elapsed": 63, "internal_node_id": "0.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 80131, "stimulus": ["<p> Welcome! </p> <p> We are conducting an experiment about how people evaluate intuitive physics situations when asked a question in plain english. Your answers will be used to inform computer science and cognitive science research.</p><p> This experiment should take no more than <strong>10 minutes</strong></p> <p>  Press any key to begin. </p>"], "response": " ", "trial_type": "html-keyboard-response", "trial_index": 1, "time_elapsed": 80198, "internal_node_id": "0.0-1.0"}, {"rt": 31832, "stimulus": ["<p>In this experiment, you will be presented with a series of images containing <strong>stacks of blocks and some simple questions.</strong></p><p>The block are stacked on a grey platform in a configuration which may or may not be stable.</p><p>In each situation, you will be asked to imagine what will occur after a sufficiently large amount of time has passed and gravity has finished acting on the stacks of blocks.", "<p>Your task will be to think about how these blocks will fall and their position <strong>after they have finished falling</strong>. Note that sometimes, you may be presented with a stable stack where no blocks will fall.<p>You will enter your answer for each question by clicking a rating on a <strong>7-point multiple choice scale</strong> ranging from <strong>1 (definitely no)</strong> to <strong>7 (definitely yes)</strong>.", "<p>You will see descriptions of <strong>24  different scenarios</strong> in total.</p><p> When you are ready, please click any key to complete a quick comprehension check, before moving on to the experiment. </p>"], "response": " ", "trial_type": "html-keyboard-response", "trial_index": 2, "time_elapsed": 112033, "internal_node_id": "0.0-2.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 27521, "response": {"Q0": "Look at images containing blocks and answer questions about what will happen in the image after gravity has acted on the blocks.", "Q1": "By selecting an option from a multiple choice scale."}, "question_order": [0, 1], "trial_type": "survey-multi-choice", "trial_index": 3, "time_elapsed": 139558, "internal_node_id": "0.0-2.0-1.0"}, {"rt": 13930, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the majority of the large blocks be on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "6", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "42", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 4, "time_elapsed": 153491, "internal_node_id": "0.0-3.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 7753, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any red blocks remaining on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "2", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "13", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 5, "time_elapsed": 161248, "internal_node_id": "0.0-4.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 6785, "response": {"Q0": 6}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "7", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "46", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 6, "time_elapsed": 168037, "internal_node_id": "0.0-5.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 118532, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be more red blocks to the left of the platform than purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "2", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "14", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 7, "time_elapsed": 286570, "internal_node_id": "0.0-6.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 44007, "response": {"Q0": 0}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the number of blocks on the platform be divisible by 3?", "box_ensemble_index": "7", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "47", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 8, "time_elapsed": 330575, "internal_node_id": "0.0-7.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 12375, "response": {"Q0": 6}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be more red blocks to the left of the platform than purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "4", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "26", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 9, "time_elapsed": 342952, "internal_node_id": "0.0-8.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 33332, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be more red blocks to the left of the platform than purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "1", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "8", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 10, "time_elapsed": 376285, "internal_node_id": "0.0-9.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 6752, "response": {"Q0": 6}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will most of the blocks have stayed on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "7", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "45", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 11, "time_elapsed": 383038, "internal_node_id": "0.0-10.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 24112, "response": {"Q0": 4}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the number of blocks on the platform be divisible by 3?", "box_ensemble_index": "6", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "41", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 12, "time_elapsed": 407151, "internal_node_id": "0.0-11.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 12268, "response": {"Q0": 4}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "1", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "10", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 13, "time_elapsed": 419422, "internal_node_id": "0.0-12.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 4884, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "6", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "40", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 14, "time_elapsed": 424308, "internal_node_id": "0.0-13.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 8206, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the majority of the large blocks be on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "1", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "12", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 15, "time_elapsed": 432517, "internal_node_id": "0.0-14.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 8866, "response": {"Q0": 6}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any red blocks remaining on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "3", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "19", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 16, "time_elapsed": 441387, "internal_node_id": "0.0-15.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 9510, "response": {"Q0": 3}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the majority of the large blocks be on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "5", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "36", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 17, "time_elapsed": 450900, "internal_node_id": "0.0-16.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 15955, "response": {"Q0": 4}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the number of blocks on the platform be divisible by 3?", "box_ensemble_index": "0", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "5", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 18, "time_elapsed": 466858, "internal_node_id": "0.0-17.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 12171, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "2", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "16", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 19, "time_elapsed": 479032, "internal_node_id": "0.0-18.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 6090, "response": {"Q0": 4}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any red blocks remaining on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "6", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "37", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 20, "time_elapsed": 485124, "internal_node_id": "0.0-19.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 11835, "response": {"Q0": 0}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be more red blocks to the left of the platform than purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "0", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "2", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 21, "time_elapsed": 496961, "internal_node_id": "0.0-20.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 12312, "response": {"Q0": 3}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be more red blocks to the left of the platform than purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "7", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "44", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 22, "time_elapsed": 509276, "internal_node_id": "0.0-21.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 9613, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the majority of the large blocks be on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "2", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "18", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 23, "time_elapsed": 518893, "internal_node_id": "0.0-22.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 5761, "response": {"Q0": 6}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the majority of the large blocks be on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "3", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "24", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 24, "time_elapsed": 524657, "internal_node_id": "0.0-23.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 15031, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any red blocks remaining on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "0", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "1", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 25, "time_elapsed": 539691, "internal_node_id": "0.0-24.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 5622, "response": {"Q0": 4}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "0", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "4", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 26, "time_elapsed": 545316, "internal_node_id": "0.0-25.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 5772, "response": {"Q0": 4}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the number of blocks on the platform be divisible by 3?", "box_ensemble_index": "5", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "35", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 27, "time_elapsed": 551091, "internal_node_id": "0.0-26.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 56316, "response": {"Q0": "7", "Q1": "3", "Q2": "Looking at the center if mass of the object in relation to the one below it", "Q3": "I'm an 8 major, so I might have some more awareness of the outcomes than average"}, "trial_type": "survey-text", "trial_index": 28, "time_elapsed": 607426, "internal_node_id": "0.0-27.0"}]